<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shiny on The CuRious Financial Risk ManageR</title>
    <link>/tags/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shiny on The CuRious Financial Risk ManageR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny portfolio</title>
      <link>/2020/11/shiny-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/11/shiny-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;/rmarkdown-libs/header-attrs/header-attrs.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I will use this post as repository of all the publicly available shiny dashboards
I have developed through time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://davidemagno.com/apps/Swap_Rates/&#34;&gt;Online Interest Rate Swap Monitor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2020-11-15-shiny-portfolio.en-us_files/SwapApp.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An online application developed using R shiny to monitor in realtime the change in the the Interest Rate Swap market by scraping the web. Source data is automatically scraped from a third party website .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://davidemagno.com/apps/ItalianCovidDashboard/&#34;&gt;Interactive Dashboard on Covid19 data in Italy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2020-11-15-shiny-portfolio.en-us_files/ItalyCovid.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interactive dashboard to track the evolution of the Covid19 contagion in Italy.
Data is automatically sourced from the official Italian Government Covid Data repository (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pcm-dpc/COVID-19&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://github.com/pcm-dpc/COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;) on a daily basis. The data reported in the dashboard is fully dependant on the original source and no additional post-processing is applied to the raw data by the author of the Dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://davidemagno.com/apps/IrishCovidDashboard/&#34;&gt;Interactive Dashboard on Covid19 data in Ireland&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/post/2020-11-15-shiny-portfolio.en-us_files/IrishCovid.png&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An interactive dashboard to track the evolution of the Covid19 contagion in Ireland.
Data is sourced both from the Irish Government open data website (&lt;a href=&#34;https://data.gov.ie/blog/coronavirus-covid-19&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://data.gov.ie/blog/coronavirus-covid-19&lt;/a&gt;) and by scraping the epidemiological pdf reports published by the Health Protection Surveillance Centre (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hpsc.ie/a-z/respiratory/coronavirus/novelcoronavirus/casesinireland/&#34; class=&#34;uri&#34;&gt;https://www.hpsc.ie/a-z/respiratory/coronavirus/novelcoronavirus/casesinireland/&lt;/a&gt;). The data reported in the dashboard is fully dependant on the original source and no additional post-processing is applied to the raw data by the author of the Dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
